stylistpick.com 2013-04-24

# Privacy Policy | Stylistpick

This is the privacy policy for www.stylistpick.com. Our website is operated by Stylefantasia Limited (trading as Stylistpick.com), which is the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy, along with our terms and conditions (and any other documents referred to in them) sets out the basis on which we will process any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us.

By using our website, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Our Privacy Policy was last updated on 14 May 2012. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat your personal data by placing a notice on our website or, where appropriate, by email. We encourage you to check back from time to time and review this policy each time you use our website, noting the date of the last update (above) so that you will always know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

Stylistpick Cookies Policy

_What are cookies?_

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit a website. By setting an anonymous, unique identifier, cookies help websites recognise returning visitors and remember their preferences. Many cookies are automatically deleted after you finish using a website. 

Cookies cannot harm your computer. They are not programmes and they cannot carry viruses or install malware on your computer.

You can learn more about cookies and how to manage them by visiting the website [www.aboutcookies.org/](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) (opens in a new window – please note that we are not responsible for the content of external websites).

_How to control and delete cookies_

Stylistpick will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However if you wish you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the web sites you visit. The help function in your browser should tell you how to do this.

Please be aware that restricting cookies may have an impact on the functionality of the Stylistpick website. For instance, to order products at Stylistpick you need to have cookies enabled, which is the default setting for most web browsers like Firefox, Chrome or Internet Explorer.

For information on how to manage cookies on your mobile phone browser, please see your handset manual.

_How Stylistpick uses cookies_

We use cookies to:

  1. Keep track of what you have in your shopping bag 
  2. Remember you when you return to our site 
  3. Count the number of visitors to our website and other site usage information 
  4. Increase the relevancy of advertising displayed to you 

We have an advertising agreement with Google who may set cookies during your visit to be used for remarketing purposes. This is so that we can serve more relevant advertising to you based on what you appear to be interested in. If you would like to opt out of remarketing cookies, including Google’s cookies, please go to the Network Advertising Initiative website (opens in a new window – please note that we are not responsible for the content of external websites). 

_List of Stylistpick cookies_  
This is a list of the main cookies set by the Stylistpick website, and what each is used for. 

**Cookie Name** | **Purpose**  
---|---  
_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz | 

Google Analytics sets cookies to help us accurately measure the number of site visitors and site usage. 

The anonymous data stored by these cookies can be seen only by the relevant teams at Stylistpick and Google and never shows any confidential information.

How to reject or delete these cookies:

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
  
qbef, _qubitTracker, _qPageNum_stylistpick_UK, _qst, _qsst, optimizelyPendingLogEvents, optimizelyEndUserID, optimizelyBuckets | 

These cookies enable the function of analytics software supplied by our business partner Qubit. This software helps us take and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, visitor numbers and shopping times. That information helps us to improve the website and your shopping experience. 

The data stored by these cookies can only be seen by the relevant teams at Stylistpick and Qubit, and never shows any confidential or personally identifiable information.  
_msuuid_ | This cookie is set by Marin Software, who provide an online advertising campaign management solution for Stylistpick.  
  
Third party cookies set for Stylistpick users:

Stylistpick uses a number of suppliers who also set cookies on the Stylistpick website on its behalf in order to deliver the services that they are providing.

**Cookie Name** | **Purpose**  
---|---  
pid | This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a ‘tweet’ button.  
PREF, VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, use_hitbox | 

These cookies are set by YouTube when you visit a page with a link to our YouTube channel.  
  
external_31914587_end_user_id | This cookie enables the function of online marketing software supplied by our business partner Qubit. See entry for Qubit above.  
_msuuid | This cookie is set by Marin Software, who provide an online advertising campaign management solution for Stylistpick.  
AWSELB, PHPSESSID | These cookies are used by our advertising partner Supersonic Ads to track website purchases.  
test_cookie | 

This cookie is set by Doubleclick (Google) to allow us to serve more relevant advertising to you. 

How to reject or delete Doubleclick cookies: 

<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>  
  
_stid, _uset | Cookies set by ShareThis, a plugin used for social media share buttons on our blog.  
UID, UIDR | This is a Scorecard Research cookie passed through the Sharethis social media plugin. To opt out of scorecard research web tagging please visit [www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx](http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx)  
  
IP addresses

When you visit our website, we may automatically collect system-related information about your visit, such as the type of internet browser and operating system you use, the website from which you have come to our website and your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. This information is collected for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. It is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and does not, of itself, contain any personally identifiable information.

Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information (such as your name, email address, postal address, payment details and telephone number) that you provide by completing forms on our website, including if you create a member account, subscribe to any of our services, order any of our products, upload or submit any material via our website or request any information.
  * Information in connection with an account sign-in facility, your login and password details.
  * Details of any transactions made by you through our website and of the fulfilment of your orders.
  * Communications you send to us, for example to report a problem or to submit queries, concerns or comments regarding our website or its content.
  * Information you provide when you complete surveys, or enter promotions or competitions that we may, from time to time, run on our website for research purposes, if you choose to respond to, or participate in, them.
  * Details of your visits to our website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access.
  * Details of your visits to our pages or presences on social networking sites (whether you access them via our website or otherwise).
  * Information you provide by accepting permissions via Facebook Connect and Stylistpick Styler (Facebook application)

Opting out of providing information

You are under no obligation to provide any such information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services and you may not be able to continue to hold a member account.

We may, from time to time, run referral programmes or similar initiatives, such as the Invite Your Friends scheme, that invites you to provide us with the contact details of someone who is known to you who may find our products or services to be of interest. By providing us with their details, you confirm that you have their permission to do so, and also that we may identify you to them as the friend who recommended them. You must not provide us with the details of anyone from whom you do not have such permission.

You can also at any time request us to delete any Facebook information that we store by sending us an e-mail at [customerservices@stylistpick.com](mailto:customerservices@stylistpick.com).

Your Facebook access token will expire after 60 days when you login again after this period our systems will then request permission for another access token.

Your personal information and how we use it

  * We will use the information held about you to do the following:
  * Enable us to process your orders and to provide you with the products, services and information offered through our website and which you request.
  * Administer your account with us, and to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * Verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; and send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our products and services, provided you have consented to be contacted for these purposes.
  * Ensure that the content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your compute.
  * Notify you about changes to our products and/or services.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (email or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those that were the subject of a previous sale to you. If you are a new customer, we will contact you only by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

  * You can tell us not to contact you with information regarding our products and services, either at the point such information is collected on our website (by checking or un-checking (as directed) the relevant box) or, where you do not wish us to continue to use your information in this way, by following the unsubscribe instructions on any communications sent to you. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us using the 'Help & Contact' page on our website.

Information sharing

We may disclose aggregate statistics about visitors to our website, customers and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, sponsors and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifiable information.

  * We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
  * We may also disclose your personal information to our affiliates, to providers of our affiliate network services, or to our agents or contractors who assist us in providing the products and services we offer through our website, processing transactions, fulfilling requests for information, receiving and sending communications, updating marketing lists, analysing data, providing support services or in other tasks, from time to time.
  * Our agents and contractors will only use your information to the extent necessary to perform their functions.
  * If we sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Stylefantasia Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, the personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions, or if we believe that such action is necessary to prevent fraud or crime or to protect our website or the rights, property or personal safety of Stylefantasia Limited, our customers or any other person. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Public forums

Our website may, from time to time, make chat rooms, message boards, news groups and/or other public forums available to its users. We also have presences on a number of social networking sites. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when using these and never disclose your personal information.

External links

Our website may, from time to time, contain links to external sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites and we suggest that you check those policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

Payment processing

Payments made on our website are made through our payment service provider. You will be providing credit or debit card information directly to our payment service provider, which operates a secure server to process payment details, encrypting your credit/debit card information and authorising payment. Information that you supply to our payment service provider is not within our control and is subject to our payment service provider's own privacy policy and terms and conditions.

Security

We place great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our users. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as we consider to be appropriate and only authorised personnel have access to personal information. Whilst we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of information will never occur, we use all reasonable efforts to prevent it.

You should bear in mind that submission of information over the Internet is never entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of information you submit via our website whilst it is in transit over the Internet and any such submission is at your own risk. It is advisable to close your browser when you have finished your user session to help ensure others do not access your personal information if you use a shared computer or a computer in a public place.

Storage of your information

Information that you submit via our website is sent to and stored on secure servers operated by or on behalf of our hosting provider. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to the third parties mentioned in the circumstances set out above (see Information Sharing).

Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting the data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking or unchecking (as directed) certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us using the Help & Contact page on our website.

You have the right under the Act to a copy of the personal information about you held by us. Your right of access may be exercised in accordance with the Act, and your request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with the details of the information we hold about you. You also have a right to correct any errors in that information.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about this Privacy Policy or any requests concerning your personal data, please contact us using the Help & Contact page on our website.
